<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TD-DFT on Mustafa Kurban, Ph.D. </title>
    <link>/tags/td-dft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TD-DFT on Mustafa Kurban, Ph.D. </description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Code with  &lt;a href=&#39;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#39;&gt;Blogdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;copy; Mustafa Kurban, {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="/tags/td-dft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New donor materials for bulk-heterojunction solar cells</title>
      <link>/project/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The performance of organic cells based on bulk heterojunctions (BHJs) has improved recently, but further improvements are necessary. In this work, we have carried out a thorough examination using density functional theory (DFT) and time-dependent (TD)-DFT to investigate the structural and optoelectronic properties of pentacene-based organic molecules (PbOMs) as potential donor material for organic photovoltaic BHJ devices. Our results show that oxadiazole prefers to attach via its nitrogen atoms to the carbon atoms of the pentacene monomer with an adsorption energy about − 32.86 kcal/mol, which means that oxadiazole is efficiently adsorbed on the edge of the pentacene. The HOMO energy level of the PbOM with the lowest bandgap is − 4.00 eV wide, i.e., about 0.86 eV lower and more positive than pentacene, thus providing an ideal open-circuit voltage for photovoltaic devices. The bandgap of the PbOM compounds are about 1.61 and 1.80 eV affording an efficient charge transfer from donor to acceptor. Furthermore, the donor PbOMs are also more stable than the pentacene. We have examined, additionally, the reactivity and absorption properties of individual molecules and PbOM systems. Our results suggest that the PbOM, as a donor material, may significantly improve the efficiency of BHJ solar cells.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hexathiopentacene (HTP) Nanorings</title>
      <link>/project/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The electronic structure and structural and optoelectronic properties of hexathiopentacene (HTP) nanorings have been carried out by density functional theory (DFT) and time-dependent DFT (TD-DFT). Herein, the binding energy per atom, ionization potential, electron affinity, chemical hardness, highest occupied molecular orbital (HOMO)–lowest unoccupied molecular orbital (LUMO) gap, refractive index, charge distributions, absorbance spectra and non-linear optical properties have been measured. The calculations on these nanorings show that the HOMO–LUMO gaps range from 1.87 eV to 1.28 eV, which corresponds to the bandgap of known photovoltaic semiconductors, while the absorbance spectrum increases from 674 nm (1.84 eV) to 874 nm (1.42 eV), which indicates that the HTP nanorings absorb more light as the nanoring size is increased. From the binding energy, the stability of the HTP nanorings is higher than that of the HTP structure. Our results show that an increase in the size may play a significant role in improving the design of optoelectronic devices based upon these HTP nanorings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
