<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mustafa Kurban, Ph.D. </title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mustafa Kurban, Ph.D. </description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Code with &lt;i class=&#39;fas fa-heart&#39;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i class=&#39;fab fa-r-project&#39;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&#39;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#39;&gt;Blogdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;copy; Mustafa Kurban, {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>/talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/slides/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;journal-articles&#34;&gt;Journal Articles&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;43- )   I. Ravaei,  S. M. Azami, M. Kurban, Niacin drug delivery by Ni cluster on graphene nano flake: DFT Study Followed by AIM and NBO Analysis, Monatshefte für Chemie - Chemical Monthly, under review, (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;42-)  I. Ravaei, S. M. Azami, M. Kurban, R. Niazmand, R. Nokhostin,  Co2-capturing ability, electronic response and hydrogen storage properties of MgO nancage by density functional theory, Applied Physics A, in submitted, (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;41-)  M. Kurban and İ. Muz, .&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0167732220312575&#34;&gt;Theoretical investigation of the adsorption behaviors of fluorouracil as an anticancer drug on pristine and B-, Al-, Ga-doped C36 nanotube&lt;/a&gt;, Journal of Molecular Liquids, 309, 113209, (2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;40-)  İ. Muz, M. Kurban and M. Dalkılıç, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.springerprofessional.de/dft-and-td-dft-studies-of-new-pentacene-based-organic-molecules-/17889704&#34;&gt;DFT and TD-DFT studies of new pentacene-based organic molecules as a donor material for bulk-heterojunction solar cells&lt;/a&gt;, Journal of Computational Electronics, in press, (2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;39-)  F. Kara, M. Kurban, and B. Coşkun, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0030402620304393&#34;&gt;Evaluation of electronic transport and optical response of two-dimensional Fe-doped TiO2 thin films for photodetector applications&lt;/a&gt;, Optik, 210, 16405(1-7), (2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;38-)  M. Kurban, T. R. Sertbakan and B. Gündüz, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.springer.com/journal/894&#34;&gt;A combined experimental and DFT/TD-DFT studies on the electronic structure, structural and optical properties of quinoline derivatives&lt;/a&gt;, Journal of Molecular Modeling, in press, (2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;37-) İ. Muz and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11664-020-08017-w&#34;&gt;Electronic transport and non-linear optical properties of hexathiopentacene (HTP) nanorings: A DFT study,&lt;/a&gt; Journal of Electronic Materials, 49,3282-3289 (2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;36-) İ. Muz, F. Göktaş and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs00214-020-2544-9&#34;&gt;3d-transition metals (Cu, Fe, Mn, Ni and Zn)-doped pentacene  π-conjugated organic molecule for photovoltaic applications: DFT and TD-DFT calculations&lt;/a&gt;, Theoretical Chemistry Accounts, 139, 23(1-8), (2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;35-) T. Zerrin, M. Kurban, Matthew M. Dickson., M. Özkan and C. Özkan, &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acsaem.9b01960&#34;&gt;Supression of the Shuttle Effect in Li-S Batteries via Magention TiO2 Thin Film at the Electrode-Electroyte Interface&lt;/a&gt;, ACS Applied Energy Materials, in press, (2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;34-) B. Köylüoğlu, S. Alei and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.worldscientific.com/doi/abs/10.1142/S0217979219503739&#34;&gt;Molecular dynamics study on composition and temperature dependences of mechanical properties of CdTeSe nanowires under uniaxial stretching&lt;/a&gt;, International Journal of Modern Physics B, 33, 1950373, (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;33-) H. Kurban, M. Kurban and M. Dalkılıç,  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2352492819307469&#34;&gt;Density-functional tight-binding approach for the structural analysis and electronic structure of copper hydride metallic nanoparticles&lt;/a&gt;, Materials Today Communications, 21, 100648(1-7), (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;32-) İ. Muz and M. Kurban,  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0925838819322959&#34;&gt;A comprehensive study of electronic structure and optical properties of carbon nanotubes with doped B, Al, Ga, Si, Ge, N, P and As and different diameters, Journal of Alloys and Compounds&lt;/a&gt;, 802, 25-35, (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;31-) M. Kurban, C. Kürkçü, Ç. Yamçıçer and F. Göktaş, &lt;a href=&#34;https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1361-648X/ab1c9e&#34;&gt;A study of structural phase transitions and optoelectronic properties of perovskite-type hydrides MgXH3: Ab initio calculations&lt;/a&gt;, Journal of Physics: Condensed Matter, 31, 305401 (1-12) (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;30-) M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0925838819312484&#34;&gt;Tunable electronic structure and structural transitions of GaAs clusters at high pressure and temperature&lt;/a&gt;, Journal of Alloys and Compounds, 791, 1159-1166, (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;29-) İ. Muz and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1230340218301331&#34;&gt;Enhancement of electronic, photophysical and optical properties of 5,5′-Dibromo-2,2′-bithiophene molecule: New aspect to molecular design&lt;/a&gt;, Opto-Electronics Review, 27, 113-118 (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;28-) C. Kürkçü, Ç. Yamçıçer and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1293255819300020&#34;&gt;Structural evolutıon and electronic properties of CaS: An ab initio study&lt;/a&gt;, Solid State Sciences, 90, 14-20 (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;27-) M. Kurban, H. Kurban and M. Dalkılıç, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dergipark.org.tr/tr/download/article-file/911324&#34;&gt;Controlling Structural and Electronic Properties of ZnO NPs: Density-Functional Tight-Binding Method&lt;/a&gt;, B. Int. J. Sci. and Tech. Res., 3, 35-39, (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;26-) M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dergipark.org.tr/tr/download/article-file/911337&#34;&gt;The Effects of A Single Atom Substitution and Temperature on Electronic and Photophysical Properties F8T2 Organic Material&lt;/a&gt;, B. Int. J. Sci. and Tech. Res., 3, 40-44, (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;25-) H. Kurban and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dergipark.org.tr/en/download/article-file/887851&#34;&gt;Study of structural and optoelectronic properties of hexagonal ZnO nanoparticles&lt;/a&gt;, BSEU Journal of Science, 6, 124-131, (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;24-) M. Kurban, B. Gündüz, F. Göktaş, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0030402619300804&#34;&gt;Experimental and Theoretical Studies of the structural, electronic and optical properties of BCzVB organic material&lt;/a&gt;, Optik, 182, 611-617 (2019).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;23-) M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dergipark.org.tr/en/download/article-file/607246&#34;&gt;Molecular Dynamics study on the structural, thermal and energetic properties of GaAs Nanoparticles, ETUJST-A-Applied Sciences and Engineering&lt;/a&gt;, 19(3), 620-627, (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;22-) E. B. Sas, M. Kurban, B. Gündüz, M. Kurt, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S037967791830376X&#34;&gt;Photophysical, spectroscopic properties and electronic structure of BND: Experiment and theory&lt;/a&gt;, Synthetic Metals, 246, 39-44, (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;21-) B. Gündüz, M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0925346718306323&#34;&gt;Photophysical and optical properties of 5-Bromo-2-nitropyridine organic molecule: Experiment and theory&lt;/a&gt;, Optical Materials, 85, 373-381 (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;20-) M. Kurban,  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0030402618309896&#34;&gt;Electronic structure, optical and structural properties of Si, Ni, B and N-doped a carbon nanotube: DFT study&lt;/a&gt;, Optik, 172, 295-301, (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19-) A. Candan, M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0038109818301777&#34;&gt;Electronic structure, elastic and phonon properties of perovskite-type hydrides MgXH3 (X = Fe, Co) for hydrogen storage&lt;/a&gt;, Solid State Communications, 281, 38-43, (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;18-) M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dergipark.org.tr/tr/download/article-file/584839&#34;&gt;Size and composition dependent structure of ternary Cd-Te-Se nanoparticles&lt;/a&gt; , T. Journal of Physics, 42, 443-454, (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;17-) S. Ö. Kotiloğlu, S. Çelik, E. Tanış, M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://chemistry-europe.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/slct.201800412&#34;&gt;Investigation of structural, vibrational properties and electronic structure of Fluorene-9-bisphenol: A DFT approach&lt;/a&gt;, ChemistrySelect, 3, 5934-5940 (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;16-) M. Kurban and B. Gündüz, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0030402618304807&#34;&gt;Electronic structure, optical and structural properties of organic 5,5′-Dibromo-2,2′-bithiophene&lt;/a&gt;, Optik, 165, 370-379 (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15-) İ. Muz and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0020169317318558&#34;&gt;Ab initio study of structural and electronic properties of SinC5-nH8 (n=0-5) series: Probing the 2D to 3D structural transition&lt;/a&gt;, Inorganica Chimica Acta, 477, 318-325 (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;14-) B. Gündüz and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0924203117303491&#34;&gt;Photonic, spectroscopic properties and electronic structure of PTCDI-C8 organic nanostructure&lt;/a&gt;, Vibrational Spectroscopy, 96, 46-51 (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;13-) İ. Muz, M. Kurban and K. Şanlı, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0020169317319424&#34;&gt;Analysis of the geometrical properties and electronic structure of Arsenide doped Boron clusters: Ab-initio approach&lt;/a&gt;, Inorganica Chimica Acta, 474, 66-72 (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12-) M. Kurban and B. Gündüz, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0020169317319424&#34;&gt;Study of structural, optical properties and electronic structure of PTCDI-C5 organic nanostructure&lt;/a&gt;, Chemical Physics Letters, 691, 14-21 (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11-) E. Tanış, E. B. Sas, M. Kurban, M.Kurt, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0022286017314035&#34;&gt;The structural, electronic and spectroscopic properties of 4FPBAPE molecule: Experimental and theoretical study&lt;/a&gt;, Journal of Molecular Structure, 1154, 301-318 (2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10-) M. Kurban and B. Gündüz, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0022286017301473&#34;&gt;Physical and Optical Properties of DCJTB Dye for OLED Display Applications: Experimental and Theoretical Investigation&lt;/a&gt;, Journal of Molecular Structure, 1137, 403-411 (2017).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1386947716313558&#34;&gt;Segregation formation, thermal and electronic properties of ternary cubic CdZnTe clusters: DFT calculations and MD simulations&lt;/a&gt;, Physica E, 88, 243-251 (2017).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8-) F. Aksoy, G. Aksoy and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/14786435.2016.1232493&#34;&gt;Microstructural properties and local atomic structures of cobalt oxide nanoparticles synthesised by mechanical ball-milling process&lt;/a&gt;, Philosophical Magazine, 96, 3211-3226 (2016).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0927025616302762&#34;&gt;Mechanical properties of CdZnTe nanowires under uniaxial stretching and compression: A molecular dynamics simulation study, Computational Materials Science&lt;/a&gt;, 122, 295-300 (2016).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6-) M. Kurban, O. B. Malcıoğlu and Ş. Erkoç, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0301010415300197&#34;&gt;Structural and Thermal properties of Zn-Cd-Te ternary nanoparticles: Molecular-Dynamics Simulations&lt;/a&gt;, Chemical Physics, 464, 40-45 (2016).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ingentaconnect.com/contentone/asp/qm/2016/00000005/00000004/art00016?crawler=true&amp;amp;mimetype=application/pdf&#34;&gt;Investigation of the structural properties of CdTe and ZnTe binary nanorods under heat treatment: Molecular Dynamics Simulations&lt;/a&gt;, Quantum Matter, 5, 602-606 (2016).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ingentaconnect.com/content/asp/jctn/2015/00000012/00000009/art00087?crawler=true&#34;&gt;Structural and electronic properties of ZnmCdnTek (m+n+k=2-4) clusters: DFT calculations&lt;/a&gt;, J. Comput. Theoret. Nanosci., 12, 1-11 (2015).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3-) M. Kurban and Şakir Erkoç, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rroij.com/peer-reviewed/structural-properties-of-znxcd1xte-x-025-050-and-075-ternary-nanorods-molecular-dynamics-simulations-34249.html&#34;&gt;Structural properties of ZnxCd1-xTe (x= 0.25, 0.50 and 0.75) ternary nanorods: Molecular Dynamics Simulations&lt;/a&gt;, Res. Rev. J. Pure Appl. Phys. 1, 35 (2013).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2-) M. Kurban, F. Göktaş, E. Karabulut and R. Tutuk, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/00268976.2011.554327&#34;&gt;Quantum Real Wave Packet Study of H(2S) + FO(2Π) → HF(1Σ+) + O(3P) Reaction on the 13A’ State&lt;/a&gt;, Molecular Physics, 109, 789 (2011).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1-) F. Göktaş, R. Tutuk and M. Kurban, &lt;a href=&#34;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/jcc.21555&#34;&gt;Time-Dependent Quantum Study of H(2S) + FO(2Π) → OH(2Π) + F(2P) Reaction on the 13A’ and 13A’’ States&lt;/a&gt; . Journal of Computational Chemistry, 31, 2607 (2010).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conference-proceedings&#34;&gt;Conference Proceedings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;42-)  E. B. Sas, M. Kurban, B. Gunduz and M. Kurt,  Evaluation of Performance of Functionals to Estimate Charge Transport Properties and Excited- State Energies, International Congress on the World of Technology and Advanced Materials (WITAM-2018), 21-23 September 2018, Kirsehir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;41-)  S. Celik, E. Tanis, S. O. Kotiloglu and M. Kurban, [Investigation of Photophysical and Toxicity Properties of Pyraclostrobin, International Congress on the World of Technology and Advanced Materials (WITAM-2018), 21-23 September 2018, Kirsehir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;40-)  S. Celik, M. Kurban, S. O. Kotiloglu and E. Tanis, Structural, thermal and vibrational properties of Poly-Hexamethylene Biguanide Hydrochloride (PHMB), International Congress on the World of Technology and Advanced Materials (WITAM-2018), 21-23 September 2018, Kirsehir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;39-)  E. Tanis and M. Kurban, S. O. Kotiloglu and S. Celik, Predicting Chemical Bioavability of Fluoxastrobin by DFT Calculations, International Congress on the World of Technology and Advanced Materials (WITAM-2018), 21-23 September 2018, Kirsehir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;38-) B. Gündüz and M. Kurban, Electronic Structure, Optical and Spectroscopic Properties of BCzVB Organic Molecule, International Conference on Physical Chemistry and Functional Materials (PCFM&amp;rsquo;18), 19-21 June 2018, p. 315, Elaziğ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;37-) B. Gündüz and M. Kurban, Controlling Photophysical Properties and Electronic Structure of PTCDI-C8 Nanostructure, International Conference on Physical Chemistry and Functional Materials (PCFM&amp;rsquo;18), 19-21 June 2018, p. 3-5, Elazığ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;36-) M. Kurban and C. Kurkcu, Unusual structural phase transition properties of GaAs Clusters under pressure, 4th International Conference on Engineering and Natural Science (ICENS), 2-6 May 2018, p. 509, Kiev, Ukranie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;35-) M. Kurban and F. Goktas, Effects of Doped Atoms on the Structural, Electronic and Optical Properties of a Carbon Nanotube, 4th International Conference on Engineering and Natural Science (ICENS), 2-6 May 2018, p. 508, Kiev, Ukranie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;34-) B. Gündüz and M. Kurban, Optoelectronic and Spectroscopic Properties of PTCDI-C5 Small Molecule for Sensor Applications. International Conference on Condensed Matter and Materials (ICCM17), 11-15 October 2017, p. 90, Adana.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;33-) M. Kurban and F. Göktaş, Investigation of Some Physical Features of GaAs Nanoparticles for Solar Cell Applications. International Conference on Condensed Matter and Materials (ICCM17), 11-15 October 2017, p. 61, Adana.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;32-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, Molecular Dynamics Simulation of Cu55 Magic Cluster on the Graphene Monolayer. International Conference on Condensed Matter and Materials (ICCM17), 11-15 October 2017, p. 120, Adana.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;31-) I. Muz and M. Kurban, The structure and energetic arsenide doped boron clusters (N=9), International Conference on Material Science and Technology in Cappadocia (IMSTEC’17), 11-13 October 2017, p. 379, Nevşehir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;30-) I. Muz and M. Kurban, Electronic properties of Co3O4 nanocluster from density-functional calculations, International Conference on Material Science and Technology in Cappadocia (IMSTEC’17), 11-13 October 2017, p. 775, Nevşehir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;29-) M. Kurban and I. Muz, Understanding the structural properties of CdTeSe nanopartricles for solar cell applications, International Conference on Material Science and Technology in Cappadocia (IMSTEC’17), 11-13 October 2017, p. 657, Nevşehir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;28-) I. Muz and M. Kurban, 2D-3D Structural Transition in SinC5-nH8 (n=0-5) Series.  International Conference on Material Science and Technology in Cappadocia (IMSTEC’17), 11-13 October 2017, p. 552, Nevşehir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;27-) S. Çelik, M. Kurban, S. Ö. Kotiloğlu and Emine Tanış, Investigation of geometrical, electronic and spectroscopic properties of Fluorene-9-phenol molecule.  III. International Turkish Congress on Molecular Spectroscopy (TURCMOS-17), 26-29 August 2017, p. 108, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;26-) S. Çelik, Emine Tanış,S. Ö. Kotiloğlu and M. Kurban, A theoretical study of solvent effects on 2-acetoxybenzoic acid molecule.  III. International Turkish Congress on Molecular Spectroscopy (TURCMOS-17), 26-29 August 2017, p. 154, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;25-)  M. Kurban and B. Gündüz, UV Characterizations of 5-Bromo-2-nitropyridine: Experimental and Theoretical Research. 4th Internatıonal conference on materials science and nanotechnology for next generation (MSNG2017), 28-30 June 2017,  p 52, Sarajevo/BOSNIA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;24-) M. Kurban and B. Gündüz, Experimental and Theoretical Study on the Electronic and Optoelectronic Properties of 5,5&amp;rsquo;-Dibromo-2,2&amp;rsquo;-bithiophene Organic Material for Photovoltaic Application.  4th International conference on materials and nanotachnology for next generation (MSNG2017), 28-30 June 2017, p. 51, Sarajevo/BOSNIA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;23-) M. Kurban, Size dependence and segregation phenomena of copper hydrid nanoparticles: A molecular dynamics study, Turkish Physical Society 32nd International Physics Conference, 6-9 September 2016, p. 298, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;22-) M. Kurban, A molecular dynamics study on the geometrical and energetics properties of Gallium-Arsenide nanoparticles under heat treatment, Turkish Physical Society 32nd International Physics Conference, 6-9 September 2016, p. 61, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;21-) B. Gündüz and M. Kurban Determination of electronic, spectroscopic and optical properties of DCJTB semiconductor by experimental solution technique and theoretical quantum mechanical method, 2nd International Advanced and Functional Materials Technologies (AFMAT), October 20-22, 2016, p. 36, Antalya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;20-) M. Kurban and B. Gündüz, Computational and experimental thin film investigations on structure, energetics and spectroscopy properties of DCJTB, 2nd International Anvanced and Functional Materials Technologies (AFMAT), October 20-22, 2016, p. 31, Antalya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19-) M. Kurban “Core and surface segregation and thermal properties of CdTe0.50Se0.50 ternary nanoparticles”, 12th International Nanoscience and Nanotechnology Conference, 3-5 June 2016, p. 98, Gebze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;18-) M. Kurban, and Ş. Erkoç, Geometrical and energetic properties of 15-atom ternary Cd-Zn-Te clusters, 9th International Physics Conference of the Balkan Physical Union, 224-27 August 2015, p. 373, Istanbul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;17-) M. Kurban, O. B. Malcıoğlu and Ş. Erkoç, ZnxCdyTez Nanoparçacıklarının Termodinamik Özelliklerinin Moleküler Dinamiği Benzetimi ile incelenmesi, 20. Yoğun Madde Fiziği Ankara Toplantısı, 26 Aralık 2014, sayfa P16, Ankara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;16-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, Proper Gaussian basis sets for density functional studies of cobalt oxide clusters, TFD31, 21-24 July 2014, p. 297, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15-) M. Kurban, O. B. Malcıoğlu and Ş. Erkoç, A molecular dynamics study of the heat capacity of CdTe and ZnTe nanoparticles, TFD31, 21-24 July 2014, p. 296, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;14-) M. Kurban, O. B. Malcıoğlu and Ş. Erkoç, Size dependence and heat capacity of CdZnTe and CdZn nanoparticles: Molecular dynamics simulations TFD31, 21-24 July 2014, p. 295, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;13-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, Structural and electronic properties of ZnmCdnTek (m+n+k=2-4) clusters: Density functional theory calculations, NanoTR9, 24-28 June 2013, p. 124, Ataturk University, Erzurum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, Structural properties of ZnTe and CdTe binary nanorods: Molecular Dynamics Simulations, 30th Internatıonal Physıcs Congress, 2-5 September 2013, p. 371, İstanbul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11-) M. Kurban and Ş. Erkoç, Structural properties of ZnxCd1-xTe (x=0.25 and 0.50) nanorods: NanoTR8, 25-28 June 2012, Hacettepe University, p. 234, Ankara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10-) M. Kurban, E. Karabulut and F. Gogtas, Time-Dependent Quantum Study of the Reaction of Hydrogen Isotopes and Flouroxide Molecule, Turkish Physical Society 27th International Physics Conference, 14-17 September 2010, p. 470, İstanbul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9-) E. Karabulut, M. Kurban, R. Tutuk and F. Gogtas., Isotope Effects in the X + LiF → XF +Li (X=H, D) Reaction, Turkish Physical Society 27th International Physics Conference, 24-27 September 2010, p. 458, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8-) M. Kurban and F.Gogtas, Quantum Wave Packet Calculation of Reaction Probabilities, Cross Section and Rate Constant for H+FO System on the 11A’ State, Turkish Physical Society 27th International Physics Conference, 14-17 September 2010, p. 471, İstanbul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7-) M. Kurban, F. Gogtas, E. Karabulut and R.Tutuk.,Time-Dependent Quantum Dynamics study of Reactive Scattering of the H+OF Reaction on the 13A’ and 13A’’ States, Turkish Physical Society 27th International Physics Conference, 14-17 September 2010, p. 469, İstanbul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6-) M. Kurban, E. Karabulut, R. Tutuk and F. Gogtas.,Quantum Real Wave packet Study of H(2S)+FO(2Π) →HF(1Σ+)+O(3P) Reaction on the 13A’ State, Turkish Physical Society 27th International Physics Conference, 14-17 September 2010, p. 468, İstanbul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5-) R. Tutuk, E. Karabulut, M. Kurban and F. Gogtas., Quantum Wave Packet Study of the H+ CaCI (v,j)→HCI (v’,j’) + Ca Reaction, Turkish Physical Society 27th International Physics Conference, 14-17 September 2010, p. 88, İstanbul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4-) E. Karabulut, M. Kurban, R.Tutuk and F. Gogtas.,Quantum Dynamics Study of H+LiF reaction, Turkish Physical Society 26th International Physics Conference, 14-17 September 2010, p 457, İstanbul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3-) R. Tutuk, E. Karabulut, M. Kurban and F. Gogtas, Time-Dependent Quantum Study of the H(2S)+FO(2Π)→OH(2Π)+F(2P) Reaction, Turkish Physical Society 26th International Physics Conference, 24-27 September 2009, p. 339, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2-) M. Kurban, E. Karabulut, R. Tutuk and F. Gogtas, The Investigation of Photo-Dissociation by Time Dependent Quantum Method, Turkish Physical Society 26th International Physics Conference, 24-27 September 2009, p. 317, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1-) M. Kurban, E. Karabulut, R.Tutuk and F. Gogtas, Quantum Wave Packet Study of D+FO Reaction, Turkish Physical Society 26th International Physics Conference, 24-27 September 2009, p. 316, Bodrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;journal-reviewer&#34;&gt;Journal Reviewer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Journal of Molecular Structure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synthetic Metals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spectrochimica Acta Part A: Molecular and Biomolecular Spectroscopy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International Journal of Modern Physics B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Material Reasearch Express&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid State Communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;J ournal of Physics: Condensed Matter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turkish Journal of Physics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applied Physics A&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International Journal of Physics of Hydrogen Energy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Journal of Nanostructure in Chemisty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nevsehir Journal of Science and Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Duzce University Journal of Science and Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
