<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carbon nanotube on Mustafa Kurban, Ph.D. </title>
    <link>/tags/carbon-nanotube/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Carbon nanotube on Mustafa Kurban, Ph.D. </description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Code with &lt;i class=&#39;fas fa-heart&#39;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i class=&#39;fab fa-r-project&#39;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&#39;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#39;&gt;Blogdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;copy; Mustafa Kurban, {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="/tags/carbon-nanotube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving drug delivery systems for healthy cells</title>
      <link>/project/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Density functional theory (DFT) is used to examine the formation possibility of a stable interaction between 5-fluorouracil (5-FU) drug molecule and a pristine, boron (B), aluminum (Al), and gallium (Ga)-doped carbon nanotube (CNT). The structural, electronic, optical and reactivity properties of mentioned complexes are investigated in detail. Adsorption energies between the CNT and 5-FU are calculated in the range of −3.79 and −4.38 kcal/mol. Herein, the adsorption of the 5-FU on B-doped CNT is very weak, while stronger adsorption takes place in the case of Al- and Ga-doped CNTs. The results mean that the Al and Ga dopant increases the adsorption capacity of CNT with enhancing its interactions with oxygen atoms of the 5-FU. The charge transfer from adsorbed the 5-FU to Al- and Ga-doped CNTs was confirmed by the natural bond orbital, Mulliken charges, FBO and LBO analyses. It is found that the adsorption of 5-FU on Al-doped CNT is relatively stronger than that of Ga-doped CNT. The NCI-RDG analyses also verify these findings. The first absorption peaks suggest that the B-, A, Ga doped CNTs can absorb in the visible light region. Finally, Al-doped CNT has more desirable properties to use it as a drug delivery system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
